

Daniel Grayson

Product Designer

6 New Heaven Avenue, Reikebulaeze Street, Eneka Rukpokwu. Port Harcourt, Rivers State

+239 9019102139 osuomordaniel@gmail.com

I am a graphic designer with years of experience in art and design adept in creating powerful visuals using digital illustrations, images, and typography. I seek challenging opportunities where I can properly use my skills not only for the success of the organisation, but also hone my skills.

Experience

2023- Present

UI/UX Designer

DivineAssistants / Toronto, Canada

Created designs for different screen types and media platforms

Improve customer satisfaction and loyalty through the utility, ease of use, and pleasure provided in the interaction with a product.

Create products that provide meaningful and relevant experiences to users

2022- Present

UI/UX Design Tutor

Web3 HUB / Port Harcourt, Nigeria

Tutor students (both graduates and undergraduates) in UI/UX and design courses

Designed websites for all device platforms

2019-2021

Lead Graphic Designer

G3 Prints Limited / Benin City, Nigeria

Brought forth advanced experience working with typography and graphic design principles.

Mentored co-workers in creative process to facilitate collaboration and quality deliverables

Worked directly with clients to produce appealing and compelling presentations that engaged target audience.

Education

Bachelor Of Science
Department Of Computer Science
University Of Port Hracourt
2019- 2023

Expertise

Illustration Branding Graphics Design Web Development UI / UX Design

Software Skills

Photoshop Adobe XD Illustrator Figma HTML / CSS

References

Augustine Nkama Orji CEO G3 Prints Limited +234 7039377353 g3printslimitedng@gmail.com